(Leonard:)Look at us, getting ready
for a double date with actual women...
(Leonard:)...who publicly acknowledge
they're our girlfriends.
Yes. I mean,
actual women are the best.
(Sheldon:)I don't understand.
What other kind of women are there?
(Leonard:)Artificial women are your department.
You wanna take this?
(Howard:)No, it would just freak him out.
(Howard:)Listen, before we leave,
I should warn you...
(Howard:)...I'm a passionate man...
(Howard:)...and I tend towards
public displays of affection.
(Leonard:)What are you trying to tell me, Howard?
There might be making out
in the car or restaurant.
(Howard:)I don't want Bernadette
to feel uncomfortable...
(Howard:)...so it would help
if you and Penny made out too.
(Leonard:)Don't worry, we're planning to have sex
right on the salad bar.
(Raj(arriving):)Namaste, white people.
Good news. I've rented us...
(Raj(arriving):)-...the four-hour edition of Watchmen.
-Got it.
(Howard:)-Seen it.
-Detailed analysis posted online.
Then what are we gonna do tonight?
Sorry. Howard and I are going out
with Penny and Bernadette.
(Howard:)Yeah, no more carefree bachelor nights
for me and Leonard.
(Howard:)These broncos have been saddled.
[IMITATES HORSE WHINNYING]
(Leonard:)How did we get actual women?
(Raj:)Great. They get girlfriends
and they just abandon us?
(Sheldon:)It is great, isn't it?
(Sheldon:)We have a wonderful evening
ahead of us.
(Raj:)-We do?
-Oh, yes.
I discovered I don't have enough room
on my hard drive for a LINUX partition.
You and I are gonna perform
a full backup, reinitialize...
(Sheldon:)...and then reinstall
all my operating systems.
-I don't wanna do that.
-All right.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm going to perform
a full backup, reinitialize...
(Sheldon:)...and then reinstall
all my operating systems.
Well, what about me?
(Sheldon:)Well, I understand there are
several types of artificial women.
(Sheldon:)Maybe you should look into that.